## JILLANA JONES

Email: <u>jillanathomas@yahoo.com</u>
Address: #15 Edinburgh Crescent Cocoyea
Contact: 1868(768-9888)

Dear Sir/ Madam

## **RE: Job Application**

I hereby apply for a suitable position at your organization. My combination of technical experience and safety policies makes me the right person for your establishment. I would like to refer to myself as a multitalented person, one that is able to adapt to any task given and complete it to the best of my ability. I am a team builder and an extremely hard working individual that is truly dedicated to the job. My training of OSHA regulations which include fire prevention plans, hazardous material handling, machine guarding, developing appropriate training programs and delivering training to employees are just some of the exceptional assets that I can offer you.

Attached below is my CV. I hope this has given you some insight into the skills and traits I possess and I am considered for the job opportunity. Thank you for your time I eagerly await your call.

Respectfully

Jillana Jones

## JILLANA JONES

Email: jillanathomas@yahoo.com

Address: #15 Edinburgh Crescent Cocoyea

**Contact:** 1868(768-9888)

## Objective

To produce quality service whilst identifying probable risks, preventing accidents and implementing safety regulations. Above all, I aim for the development of an organization and its people

#### **Education:**

- NEBOSH Full Certification in Health and Safety Management.
- OSHA Full Certification in General Industry Occupational Safety & Health
- OSHA P.L.E.A Safety training
- OSHA Basic Safety

## Pleasantville Secondary

- English
- History
- Geography
- Human and Social Biology.

Company	Position Held	Year
Trinweld Contractors Ltd	Safety Officer	2016-2013
Structural and Mechanical	Fire Watch Officer	2013 -2012
Agencies Ltd		
Chicago Bridge and Iron	Safety Officer	2009-2012
Ltd		
I.C.C.S Contracting Ltd	Safety Officer	2008-2009

# JILLANA JONES

Email: <u>iillanathomas@yahoo.com</u>

Address: #15 Edinburgh Crescent Cocoyea

**Contact:** 1868(768-9888)

Trinity Housing	Form Setter/ General Worker	2008-2007/2004
Physical P. R Services Ltd	Clerical Assistant	2003-2004

## References

Anthony Thomas
 Trinweld Contracting services (Assistant Superintendent)
 1868 (786-3006

Anthony Francois
 Chicago Bridge and Iron (Superintendent)
 1868 (496-1069)